Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/aluh-johnsonsunday-138982142 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

.NET in Azure Adobe Creative Suite MySQL

Certifications

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Al Foundations

Programming Foundations: Secure Coding

Software Architecture: From Developer to Architect

Aluh Johnson Sunday

full stack software developer

Lagos Mainland, Lagos State, Nigeria

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Mobile/web Application Development, Instructional Design/multimedia, and UI/UX designer. Strong technical skill set in ASP.net C#, javascript with educational experience in teaching, training and learning.

Experience

Business & Software Solution Consulting Software Engineer October 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months) Lagos State, Nigeria

izifin

Back End Developer April 2022 - August 2022 (5 months) Lagos, Nigeria

Codebase Technologies Itd Software Engineer / training coordinator July 2020 - August 2022 (2 years 2 months) Lagos, Nigeria

Asp.net MVC/.net core (C#)

BlueChip Technologies Software Developer November 2021 - May 2022 (7 months) Lagos, Nigeria

The Bulb Africa
Back End Developer
September 2021 - November 2021 (3 months)
Lagos, Nigeria

Aptech Education

Multimedia and software Trainer

June 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Lagos

Trainer

Multimedia service solution

Asp.Net mvc C#

Key Learning Solutions
Parttime Tutor
December 2018 - May 2019 (6 months)
Lagos

Tutoring creative art and presentation, 2/3D graphics design and animation, IT consultant

Bincom Dev Center Scholarship Holder March 2019 - April 2019 (2 months) Yaba lagos

Mobile app development and design

TTC Mobile, Lagos Certified telecom associate. Trainee November 2018 - March 2019 (5 months) Ikeja, lagos

Network management
Transmission engineering
Cellular network engineering
NOC technical support
CCNA (Routing and switching)

JOS ELECTRICITY DISTRIBUTION PLC NYSC. IT Support Engineer and billing officer July 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 1 month)

biocommunication nig ltd Software Engineer January 2017 - June 2017 (6 months) Lekki, Lagos

Front end developer:

Education

Federal university of agriculture, makurdi Bachelor of Science - BS, Mathematics and Computer Science · (2011 - 2014)

ASCOE, Azare, Bauchi State, Nig (Affiliate of UNIMED) PGDE, Education · (2017 - 2018)